upnautoresponse.com 2014-03-19

# Ultimate Profits Network

NOTE: In this entire section UPN refers to Ultimate Profits Network

At Ultimate Profits Network we care how information about you is used and shared and we appreciate your trust.

By visiting any of the sites offered by Ultimate Profits Network you are accepting the practices described in this PRIVACY POLICY.   

**Information You Give Us:**

> Your information collected is solely for the use of Ultimate Profits Network and will not be sold to any other company or third parties.
> 
> We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, providing our services and communicating with you.  
> 

**Automatic Information:**

> We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies" and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our sites. Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) click stream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  
> 

**What About Cookies?**

> Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. Besides using the information as described above, UPN utilizes cookies to control the flow of the ordering processes by maintaining the state of your online transactions.
> 
> Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site. For Example, Payment Processors, Web Host Companies, Domain Registry etc.
> 
> However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.  
> 
> 
> **Does Ultimate Profits Network Share My Information with Others?**
> 
> Partners: We partner with other parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services.
> 
> EXAMPLE of Partners:- We may engage other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf or Business Partnership like GoDaddy.com, Trafficwave.net and Others
> 
> Examples May include But Not Limited To Processing Membership Fees, Processing Credit Card payments, providing marketing and products support and assistance, providing customer services, providing lead capture and autoresponder services, sending and receiving postal mail and email to you, removing repetitive information from customer lists, and analyzing data. These persons have access to personal information needed to perform their functions. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information that you provide to Ultimate Profits Network for any secondary purposes.
> 
> Service Providers: We engage other companies and individuals to perform enhanced services on our behalf. For example, we have engaged third parties company for member Domain Registrations and Web Host Reseller Services And Lead Capture and Autoresponders Manager. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
> 
> Business Transfer: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or their assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. 
> 
> EXAMPLE:- If Ultimate Profits Network or all or substantially all of its assets were ever to be acquired, customer/member information will of course be one of the transferred assets. 
> 
> Compliance: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Services Agreement and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Ultimate Profits Network our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.   
> 

**How Secure Is My Information?**

> We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input and the information we may send to our agents. 
> 
> UPN has gone to great lengths to ensure your information is securely obtained and not easily accessible by unauthorized Third Parties.
> 
> It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.  
> 

**What Information Can I Access?**

> Ultimate Profits Network gives you access to certain information about you for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. To view or change this information, log-in to your account to update information

**Links**

> Sites provided by Ultimate Profits Network contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the UPN web site. 

**Age Requirement**

> Ultimate Profits Network does not sell services or Memberships to anyone under the age of 18.
> 
> If you are under 18, you may use our services only with involvement of a parent or guardian.  
> 

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

> If you choose to become a Member of Ultimate Profits Network your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms and Conditions. If you have any concern about privacy at UPN, please send us a thorough description to ([admin@ultimateprofitsnetwork.com](email:admin@ultimateprofitsnetwork.com)) and we will try to resolve it. 
> 
> The Nature of Internet Marketing and Rules and regulations governing Internet Marketing and Our Business keep on changing from time to time.
> 
> In Case of Any Changes to Our Policies and Or Terms and Conditions, we may e-mail periodic reminders and or changes to our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to. You should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. 
> 
> Please Read Our FULL Terms and Conditions (Conditions of Use) by visiting the Link Below
>
>> #### **Ultimate Profits Network Terms and Conditions**  
> 

**Disclaimers to Member's Privacy**

> The UPN website may contain links to other websites. All links are provided for informational purposes only. If you click on one of these links you MAY BE ACCESSING ANOTHER WEBSITE.
> 
> You are encouraged to read and follow their terms and conditions as they may differ from ours. Your email address may be shared with your upline and downline. It may be used for educational motivational purposes only. 
> 
> All communication conducted via our communication tools are considered non-confidential and non-proprietary. Ultimate Profits Network reserves the right to publish any of the information that is transmitted via our communication tools. 
> 
> The use of this service and site(s) is at your own risk. Ultimate Profits Network will not be held liable for any loss from your lack of access to any of our sites or loss of information contained on our servers.
> 
> Any 3rd party links, text Ads and banner ads are not monitored by UPN. When you visit them you do so at your own risk.
> 
> Any personal information you disclose via Internal Mailer to downlines or uplines can be viewed by others. Do not disclose anything you do not want others to see.
> 
> All members are responsible for the confidentiality of their member log in name and password. Ultimate Profits Network and it's employees cannot be held liable for any breeches in security.
> 
> All members agree to receive emails from Ultimate Profits Network from time to time, as well as from their Team Members.
